辛普森一家
第二十三季  第五集
SPS 辛普森一家字幕组倾情呈现
仅供学习交流之用 严禁用于商业用途
Bart 的兑奖罐    Lisa 的兑奖罐
这颗弹珠是对 Lisa 打扫了自己房间的奖励
And here's a marble for Lisa for cleaning her room,
这颗弹珠是对 Bart 没把 Lisa 房间弄乱的奖励
and a marble for Bart for not trashing Lisa's room.
翻译: 旗木 偏执绝非过错 大曦瓜 微言
校对: 偏执绝非过错   时间轴  监制: MarcoII
两个罐子都满了 所以你们赢得了
The jars are full, so you've earned
周六惊喜老爹日
your Saturday Surprise Dad Day!
本周六 给你们带来过公墓彩蛋和实路微型赛车的老爹
This Saturday, from the dad who brought you cemetery paintball
and go-karts on real roads,
SPS 辛普森一家字幕组 诚招翻译时间轴压制
参与字幕制作加 QQ 群 94093420
将带你体验史上最最震撼的活动
comes the greatest activity yet...
奢华电玩展 会展中心
电玩展万岁
Video game convention!
暴怒的飞鸟
炸药 即将落成:儿童医院
瞧瞧这是啥
And check these out.
贵宾卡通行
VIP passes!
还有比插队更爽的事嘛?
Is there any better feeling than cutting in line
就凭这证明尊贵身份的塑料卡
because a plastic badge says you're special?
贵宾专用通道
侠盗猎挠手
GTS!
好多游戏啊
So many games!
GS电视游戏机(恶搞PS3)
静视(恶搞动视)
Krusty 世界(恶搞魔兽世界)!?
W.O.K.?!
飞翔的番茄
Ooh, the Flying Tomato.
生命之树在线版
Ah! TMTOLO!
特权驾照
DL2L-to-D!
刺客信条-夏日之爱
Oh! ACSOL!
人体蜈蚣?!
HC1?!
肠道大战II: 穿肠破肚
Whoa! Guts of War Two: Entrails of Intestinox!
猛抽结肠
Colon slash!
杀掉直肠
Rectum kill!
我们开发的游戏就算是神级的宅男...
We've made a game that'll reward the hardcore gamer
也得花上数千小时才能...
with hundreds and hundreds of hours of...
搞定
Finished it.
胜利
但为这个游戏 我婚都离了
But working on this game cost me my marriage.
我 我连自己的双胞胎孩子都还没见
I-I have twins I've never met!
那你见着了一定得告诉他们 你的游戏太弱智了
Well, when you meet them, tell them your game's too easy.
这个游戏包含了最好的大学军乐队
This game has all the best college marching bands.
上有节奏精准的俄亥俄州立大学乐队
From the precision footwork of Ohio State
下有没法入耳的蹩脚斯坦福大学乐队
to the lame, dead-on-arrival humor of Stanford.
我的人气在下降(观众热情)
Uh-oh, I'm losing the crowd!
闯关成功
Level cleared.
下一关 在12小时的回家巴士上备考化学测验
Next level: study for chemistry test on 12-hour bus ride home.
这真是史上最好玩的游戏
This is the funnest game ever!
天啊 这游戏要花多少币啊?
Man, how many quarters does this game take?
老爸 再过三分钟 任地狱就要在G展厅发布最新游戏平台了
Dad! Funtendo is unveiling their new system
in three minutes,in Hall G!
而我们在D展厅
And we're in Hall D.
隔三个厅 剩三分钟
Three halls, three minutes.
看老爸的
No problem.
闯关目标:限定时间内护送 Bart 和 Lisa 抵达G展厅
还剩：2次尝试机会 0次内急解决机会
都给我让开 闪边 （生命值）
Out of my way! Move it!
你们这群宅男都给我等正常人让道
Geeks must yield to normals!
已满员（G展厅）(飞盘 手枪 撬棍 灭火器）
Room's full.
任地狱 Zii
闯关成功 积分表 宅人击杀数: 23/100 伤人数: 7/10
隐藏要素: 0/10 裤链被拉下次数: 1
踩到他人的脚: 153/153 跳过多少矮子: 16
碰到胸的次数: 6/7 剩余时间: 5秒 道歉次数: 0 护送孩子存活数: 2
展览会酷毙了
Conventions rock!
给力老爹酷毙了
Fun Dad rocks!
我要睡一会儿
I need a nap!
你俩今天玩得够尽兴了
You kids have had a big day.
气球泄气 回家洗澡
Head up to the tub while I deflate your toys.
给力老爹救我们
Save us, Fun Dad!
明显孩子们跟你玩得很开心
The kids sure had a good time with you.
是啊 我今天很在状态
Yeah, I was on today.
还不是一般的在状态啊
Scary on.
怎么孩子从不叫我给力老妈?
How come they never call me Fun Mom?
听着 亲爱的 家就像个团队
Look, honey, a family's like a team.
既然是团队 就得既有扣篮巨星
And on every team, you have the slam-dunking megastar
又有裁判员
and the referee.
这不公平
It's not fair.
妈妈也想给力起来 却一直被婆婆妈妈的玩意纠结着
Moms want to be fun, but we're stuck with all the mom stuff.
好啦好啦 这么着吧
Okay, okay, how about this:
下礼拜你陪孩子过周六惊喜老爹日
next week, you take the kids on a Saturday Surprise Dad Day.
你说...
What if...
拿着零钱去逛一元店好不好?
we roll pennies and go to the dollar store?
很好啊 Marge
That's good, Marge!
脑子里还有什么烂主意赶紧都清出去
Get all the terrible ideas out of your system.
有了
I've got it!
周六惊喜老妈日带给你们 劲爆游戏
Your Saturday Surprise Mom Day is the X-Games!
也 劲爆游戏 劲爆游戏
Yay! X-Games! X-Games!
赞死啦
All right!
这看起来一点都不劲爆呢 妈
That isn't an "X," Mom.
欢迎来到基督十字游戏展 Simpson 一家
Welcome to the Cross Games, Simpsons.
这可是基督徒们一起创立的展览会
A Christian fellowship expo!
这儿有半个游戏吗?
Are there at least games here?
你搞错了 "游戏" 代表的是
Oh, no, "games" stands for
福音运动美国使者剧集地
Gathering of American Messengers for Evangelical Sports.
运动?
Sports?
"运动" 不代表运动 而是严格的家长监督
"Sports" stands for
Strict Parental Oversight Rather Than Sports.
来嘛 宝贝们 快乐来自内心
Come on, kids, fun comes from inside.
不在于我们具体做什么
It isn't about what we actually do.
当然在于了
Yes, it is!
我们本来就是通过这来找乐子的
That's all it is!
说得对 说得对 说得对
You're right, you're right, you're right.
那我们走吧
Let's go.
感谢上帝
Thank the Lord!
可以在《不公道管家》里扮演罪人的小孩(《福音书》中的耶稣寓言)
Two children to play debtors
可以在《不公道管家》里扮演罪人的小孩（《福音书》中的耶稣寓言）
in the Parable of the Unjust Steward.
其他孩子都去什么劲爆游戏展了
All the other kids are at something called the X-Games.
很抱歉 筒子们
I'm sorry, gang.
都怪我搞砸了你们的周末
I blew it.
我不喜欢大人把孩子叫"筒子"
I hate it when grown-ups call kids "gang."
别太在意 老妈
Don't worry about it, Mom.
下周老爸会带我们出去补回来的
Dad will take us on a great outing next weekend.
为啥那些老松鼠总跑到我的发动机里自杀?
Why do old squirrels always crawl into my engine to die?
恐怕我们不得不改变计划 临时停车了 筒子们
Guess we'll be making an unscheduled pit stop, gang.
我们不是筒子 他们很酷的
We're not a gang! Gangs are cool!
老妈 这是什么地方?
Uh, Mom, where are we?
没什么好怕的
Nowhere scary.
一切安好
Everything's fine.
接下来我们只要等辆拖车了
We'll just wait here for the tow truck.
那个婴儿居然带耳环
That newborn has earrings!
老妈 我们饿了
Mom, we're hungry.
我想我们还是下车
I guess we could make a sprint
到这些本土小餐馆吃点东西果腹吧
for one of these local establishments.
他们居然用煎饼来夹食物
They're using pancakes as spoons.
快去看看他们还有没别的花样来吃东西
Ooh, let's see what else they do wrong.
他们居然在餐馆里卖唱片
They're selling CDs in the restaurant!
快回车上去
Back to the car!
有什么能为您效劳的吗?
What can I get you?
一份沙拉当配菜就行啦
Oh, I'll just have a side salad.
我们不提供当配菜的沙拉
We have no side salad.
快回车上去
Back to the car!
别紧张 老妈
Relax, Mom.
试试也无妨
Be adventurous.
对啊 就当玩玩嘛
Yeah, just have fun.
老爸肯定会试试的
Dad would.
你们这最赞的菜是什么?
What's the craziest thing on the menu?
她是问招牌菜
She means the most authentic.
那就推荐你
Well, that would be
特大号煎饼卷拼盘吧
the Zelzel Minchet Aletcha Wat.
那么给我们来一份
Then I'll have that!
没事 Marge
Okay, Marge,
你就当是拿敞篷车试车 你一定能行的
you test-drove a convertible once; you can do this.
我的老天爷
Holy casserole-y!
味道棒极了
That's good gloop!
真希望我能住在埃塞尔比亚
I wish I lived in Ethiopia!
美味无比 还是素食
Exotic, vegetarian,
我可以把这写到我的大学论文里去
I can mention it in a college essay.
老妈 这东西棒极了
Mom, this is amazing!
等等 她吃的那道菜是什么?
Wait, wait, wait,what is she eating?
他们可从来没给我上过这道菜
They've never served me that dish,
我可是入乡随俗戴着他们的兜帽呢
and I wear indigenous beaded headgear.
你说这个?
Oh, this?
这只不过是份特大号煎饼卷拼盘罢了
It's just a little Zelzel Minchet Aletcha Wat.
这是我唯一在这里吃过的东西
It's all I ever eat here.
他们居然给她上了菜单上没有翻译出来名称的菜
They have prepared her a dish from the non-translated page!
你们也拿份煎饼来分杯羹吧
So grab a pancake and slurp some slop!
美食家们 听我一言
Foodies,heed my call!
都来这儿敞开肚子大吃特吃吧
Commence ripping and dipping!
那么 你们的车子是不是都抛锚了?
So, did all of your cars break down?
老妈 他们可不是误打误撞来这的
Mom, they're here on purpose.
他们是美食家呢
They're foodies.
一点不错
Indeed.
我们热衷于搜寻各种美食
Our passion is to seek out interesting foods,
尽享它们的美味 然后写在博客里
savor their exotic flavors,then blog about them.
就像这样
Yes.
我们还在这里找到了韩国料理
We discovered Korean barbeque in this town.
在韩国人之前找到的?
Uh, before the Koreans?
料理确实是他们做的 但是他们还是落在咱们后面了
Oh, sure they cook it,but they don't get it.
当你把煎饼送进朋友嘴中时 它就是卷饼了
"When you stick a pancake into a friend's mouth, it's a goorsha."
大家都来吃卷饼吧
Everybody goorsha!
卷饼
Goorsha!
卷饼 卷饼 卷饼 卷饼
Goorsha! Goorsha! Goorsha! Goorsha!
Goorsha! Goorsha!Goorsha! Goorsha!
卷饼
Goorsha!
Marge 孩子们又在掐架了
Marge, the kids are acting ethnic!
别担心 Homie
Relax, Homie.
尝尝剩下的这些卷卷卷卷卷卷卷卷饼吧
Have some leftover Galalalalalalalalah.
不要
Oh, no.
我只尝我之前尝过的东西 不然我坚决不沾
I don't eat anything new unless I've eaten it before.
拜托啦 老爸 当个吃货也无妨嘛
Aw, come on, Dad, be a foodie.
你已经是个肥货和喝货了
You're already a fatty and a drunkie.
我不想让自己天天想着吃吃喝喝 我只想简简单单地喜欢美食
I don't want to think about food, I want to like it.
我们家窗户正对着四家不同的Krusty汉堡店
Why drive across town to savor a bowl of mystery mush
为啥我们还要大费周折
when there's four different Krusty Burgers
开车到镇子另一边只为一碗迷魂汤?
we can see from our house?
这才是我最喜欢的餐厅 冰箱
Oh, and here's my favorite restaurant: La Fridge.
二十四小时全天候开放 衣冠不整照样能进进出出
It's open 24 hours a day and there's no dress code.
作为美国人
What kind of American man
我们怎么能不对世界各国的饮食文化好好探索一番?
doesn't want to explore global food culture?
把我们的经历写到博客上
And then brag about it on the Internet.
不如我们自己开个美食博客吧
We should start our own food blog.
三张吃货嘴
The Three Mouthketeers.
三张?
Three?
你是说 你 他 还有我?
You mean, one, two... me?
* 我们用博客记录味蕾的舞动 *
* We're blogging a food blog *
* Marge Bart Lisa 现在是一道 *
* Marge and Bart and Lisa as one now *
* 享受美食的乐趣 *
* We're having fun now *
* 为美食如痴如狂 *
* Throwing down mad foodie game *
* 记下掌勺的大名 *
* Knowing all the chefs' names *
* 驱车驶进小韩国 *
* Rolling into K-town *
* 泡菜饭和烤肉 *
* Bibimbap and bulgogi *
* 辣椒酱让我难舍 *
* The hotties that I chill with *
* 再配上韩国泡菜 *
* Sriracha and kimchi *
* 给我秘制酱肉 *
* Give me house-made terrines *
* 配上香熏鸭腿 *
* My duck is always confit *
* 我用两千九百万瓦的余热 来烧糊我的炖肉 *
* I braise with a billion more BTUs than I need *
* 用垃圾袋包着火鸡 烤出感恩节的盛宴 *
* Cook Thanksgiving turkey in a trash bag, sous-vide *
* 从Brindisi(意大利城市)快递来的意式香肠 *
* A fumatore in Brindisi FedEx me salami *
* 如果没有甜筒 就别填满雪糕 *
* Don't scoop gelato unless it's got umami *
* 我真挚有如 Frank Bruni(美国美食评论员) 严格有如 Ruth Reichl(美国美食作家) *
* I'll be frank like Bruni,ruthless like Reichl *
* 娴熟有如 Wiley Dufresne(美国著名厨师) *
* Wiley like Dufresne *
* 当我拿起麦克风 合起音乐的节奏 *
* And when I take the mic out, Rhyme about radicchio *
* Colicchio(美国著名厨师)也要自愧不如 *
* Criticize Colicchio *
* 酒馆都有美食 *
* Every pub is gastro *
* 我做的牛肉皆上乘 *
* All my beef carpaccio *
* 把它们倒进去 朋友 *
* Throw it in the pho, yo *
* 可别说它逊色 *
* And don't you call that pho pho *
* 再尝尝美味的包子 *
* Talk about broth-squirting dumplings *
* 包子 包子 包子 *
* Dumplings,dumplings, dumplings *
* 这是我们的美食博客 *
* We're blogging a food blog *
* logging a food blog *
* 上传我们的照片 *
* Uploading pics with *
* 和我们的给力老妈一道 给力老妈 给力老妈 *
* With Our Fun Mom, Fun Mom,Fun Mom. *
大家一定会爱死我们推荐的
People are loving our list of
春田99家最好吃的阿富汗餐馆
of Springfield's top 99 Afghan restaurants.
对于那些不打折的餐馆 我深表遗憾
I feel bad for all those places that didn't make the cut.
得了吧 吃货们 面对现实吧
All right, food nerds, reality check.
那些照片里的食物都已经变成粑粑了
All the food in those pictures is poop by now.
思想升华了吧 不客气啦
Minds blown, you're welcome.
我得提醒你们一下什么才是真正的乐趣
I'll remind you kids what real fun is.
你们好啊 孩子们
Hey, hey, kids!
Krusty 乐园有了全新的游乐设施
Krustyland has a new ride.
眼球的死亡之旅
The Eyeballs of Death.
以三比二的选票有惊无险的通过了安全委员会检查
It only passed the safety panel by a three-to-two vote.
而且第三票价值不菲哦
And that third vote didn't come cheap.
我可买到星期六晚上盛大开幕式的票哦
And I've got tickets for the grand opening Saturday night.
for the grand opening Saturday night.
太棒了
Whoa! Cool.
孩子们 别忘了周六晚上我们的特别计划哦
Uh, kids, don't forget about our special plans Saturday night.
对不起 爸爸
Oh, sorry, Dad.
我们的博客人气大涨
Our blog is so popular,
我们收到了镇里最有特色的餐馆的邀请
we got an invitation to the most exclusive restaurant in town.
就连 Kent Brockman 也就只能预约到5:30或者9:30的位子
Kent Brockman himself could only get a reservation at 5:30 or 9:30.
这家店叫做化学膳房
It's called El Chemistri,
他们是运用科学来制作食物
and they use science to make the food.
看呀...松针冰糕
Behold... pine needle sorbet.
松针...冰糕?
Pine needle... sorbet?
松针冰糕?
Pine needle sorbet?
我的孩子是不会吃什么冰糕的 他们吃果子露
My kids do not eat sorbet; they eat sherbet.
而且嘴里念成"果子露"
And they pronounce it "sherbert,"
心里却想成冰淇淋
and they wish it was ice cream.
对不起 爸爸 这是我们的兴趣所在
Sorry, Dad, this is our thing now.
拉倒吧 放"给力老爹"的鸽子
Fine, blow off Fun Dad
去吃你的八字胡和炸糊了的小精灵
and go eat your walrus mustaches and deep-fried pixie wangs.
可耻的快乐 八字胡
别妒忌 Homie
Don't be so jealous, Homie,
孩子们最后选择和我一块找乐子
just because the kids are finally having fun doing something with me.
妒忌? 我会妒忌?
Aah! Jealous? Me?
太可笑了
That is to laugh.
怎么会有这种想法
The very idea.
如果有什么事...
If anything...
- 你才是会妒忌的那一个 - 我妒忌什么?
-you're the one who's jealous. -Of what?
妒忌我给孩子们带来的快乐
Of how much fun I am to be around!
和"给力老爹"一起总是快乐时光
It's always a party with Fun Dad!
太伤心了 走不动了
Too sad to walk.
太伤心太欢乐了 走不动了
Too sad and fun to walk.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
当我伤心的时候 我就会做球棒
When I'm sad, I make baseball bats.
Homie 我真心不想让你觉得被我们排斥
Homie, I don't want you to feel excluded.
你想和我们一起去
Would you like to come with us
化学膳房共进晚餐吗?
to dinner at El Chemistri?
真的吗?
Really?
你让我加入你们的活动?
You'd let me in on your thing?
就算我认为这是件很傻的事儿?
Even though I think it's stupid?
当然愿意
Of course.
把那把锯子递给我 Marge
Hand me that saw, Marge.
为什么?
Why?
当我感到快乐的时候 我会做鸟巢
When I'm happy, I make birdhouses.
孩子们 猜一猜
Kids, guess what.
妈妈邀请爸爸和你们一起去享受晚餐
Mom invited me to your fancy dinner.
真好 太棒了
Cool. Awesome!
我认为"给力老爹"现在已经变成吃货了
I guess Fun Dad is a foodie now.
吃货老爹 吃货老爹 吃货老爹
Food Dad! Food Dad! Food Dad!
我是吃货坏男孩 Tony Bourdain(美国著名厨师 作家)
I'm food bad boy Tony Bourdain.
我会去任何地方吃任何东西
There's nowhere I won't go and nothing I won't eat,
只要你用绿宝石来付我的出场费
as long as I'm paid in emeralds
给我住酒店要配有能喷出热香槟的浴盆
and my hotel room has a bidet that shoots warm champagne.
我正在新加坡小吃市场的现场
I'm here at a Singapore street-food market
和著名的美食评论家庭"三张吃货嘴"一起
with famous blogging family, the Three Mouthketeers.
Marge 你必须得尝尝这个烤鳐鱼
Marge, you've got to try some of this hang hir kuay chap.
超级麻辣的烤鳐鱼 肚子里还填满了猪肥肚
Ooh, triple spicy barbecued stingray stuffed with pig organs.
给力老爹变吃货了
Fun Dad is a foodie now!
这是我的地盘 而且永远都是
This is my thing and always will be.
吃货老爹 吃货老爹 吃货老爹
Food Dad! Food Dad! Food Dad!
和 Homer 在一起 什么事情都变的更欢乐了
Everything's more fun with Homer.
但这是我唯一拥有的啊
But this was all I had.
别在那哭哭啼啼的 Marge
Stop your bloody whinging, Marge.
是你 Gordon Ramsay (《地狱厨房》里的名厨)
Aah! Gordon Ramsay!
你搞砸了一切 蓝脑袋 难道不是吗?
You fucked it up, big blue, didn't you?
你为什么要邀请 Homer
Why did you invite Homer?
他偷走了你的王牌
He stole your bloody thunder.
你可比不上他有趣
You're not as fucking fun as him,
而且你永远都比不上
and you never will be.
亲爱的 亲爱的 哭泣可一点也不给力
Darling, darling, crying's not fun.
Homer 才给力
Homer's fun.
好了 滚出我的梦
Now, get out of my dream.
这是我的梦
It's my dream.
已经不再是了
Not anymore it's not.
Ramsay 快醒醒
Ramsay, awake.
刚才那是怎么一回事儿?
What in the hell was that?
我最给力 我最给力 我最给力
Fun me. Fun me. Fun me.
孩子们 我还在想 带上你们老爸
Kids, I was thinking, was it really such a great idea
一起去吃晚宴到底妥不妥当?
to invite your father to that dinner?
轻松点 老爸一定能为晚宴注入活力的
Relax-- Dad will be the life of the party.
他会成为第四张吃货嘴的
He'll be the fourth Mouthketeer.
但是书里根本就没四个火枪手
But there weren't four Musketeers.
阿托斯 波尔多斯 阿拉米斯 还有达达尼昂(前三人为三个火枪手 达达尼昂为书中主角 三个火枪手的好友)
Yeah-huh. Athos, Porthos,Aramis and D'Artagnan.
达达尼昂根本不是火枪手中的一个
D'Artagnan wasn't a Musketeer.
他只有一封给火枪队队长的介绍信而已
He only had a letter of introduction
而且他还把这信给弄丢了
to the captain of the guards-- which he lost!
你知道吗 我对这次特别的晚宴十分期待
You know, I'm pretty excited about this far-out dinner.
也许我会喜欢它的
Maybe I'll like it.
我不觉得
Oh, I doubt it.
你要和一堆嬉皮一起坐在一张长桌跟前
You sit at communal tables full of hipsters.
事实上 现在我倒很理解那些嬉皮
Well, actually,I've come around on hipsters.
他们能一直戴同一顶帽子 真是勇气可嘉
Takes a lot of guts to all wear the same hat.
那些食物都会被做成古怪的泡沫状
And the food will all be weird foams--
用化学药剂调味或是放在试管里端上来
cooked with chemicals or served in a test tube.
恐怕你根本就吃不下
It's too crazy for you.
听上去确实有点怪异
So it's weird.
不过别担心 我会给自己找点乐子的
Don't worry, I'll make it fun.
的确 你一直都是这样
Yeah, you always do.
那你到这来找我们
Well, here's where to meet us.
1501 西...
1501 W...
东橡树大街
East Oak Street.
东橡树大街 是这个吗
East Oak Street.Is that it?
呃 是的
Uh... yes.
好 东橡树大街
Yes, East Oak Street.
这就是你要去的地方
That's where you should go.
到时见
See you there.
别对我评头论足
Don't you judge me.
省点劲对着保姆皱眉头吧
Ah, save it for the sitter.
欢迎来到化学膳房
Welcome to El Chemistri.
请把这片薄荷糖含在嘴里
Please place these mints in your mouth,
等你们可以用膳时 薄荷糖会发出震动
and when your table is ready,they will vibrate.
就是这了: 东橡树大街 1501号
Here it is: 1501 East Oak.
门上名牌都没有 真时髦
No name on the door-- very trendy.
你想干嘛?
What do you want?
这里就是你们做出那些不可思议菜肴的化学厨房吗
Is this the chemical kitchen place where you do the crazy cooking?
小声点 伙计
Quiet, man.
好戏开始啦
The experience begins.
老爸去哪儿了?
Where's Dad?
我不知道
Uh...I don't know.
也行他改变主意
Probably changed his mind
去别的地方吃甜甜圈了
and stopped off for doughnuts.
在你们面前的是解构了的凯撒沙拉
Before you is a deconstructed Caesar salad:
生菜凝胶 蛋黄冰晶
romaine lettuce gel,egg yolk ice,
面包片泡沫以及凤尾鱼气体
crouton foam and anchovy air.
请你们按照这个顺序享用
You eat it like this:
凝胶 冰晶 泡沫 气体 泡沫 冰晶 凝胶 气体
gel, ice, foam, air,foam, ice, gel, foam, air.
就像 Marge说的一样-- 化学物质和试管
Just like Marge said-- chemicals and test tubes.
开放式的厨房真是个不错的体验
The open kitchen is a nice touch.
我想我能在我家人来之前尝尝鲜
I guess I'll get started before my family gets here.
尝一口多少钱?
How much for a taste?
只要让我开开胃就行了
You know,just to get me going.
50美元
50 bucks.
这个地方真是太棒了
Ouch. This place is fancy.
下一道菜是悲痛之汤
The next course is Regret.
看看这些嬉皮士
Hipsters.
酷得连学校都不用去
Too cool for school.
你看起来一点也不像喜欢这玩意的人
You don't look like the kind of guy who does this.
的确 我妻子也认为这个对我来说太疯狂了
Well, my wife thinks it's too crazy for me,
但我要证明她错了
but I'm goingto prove her wrong.
我这么做是为了我的家庭
I'm doing this for my family.
好了 瘾君子们 交出你们的冰毒
All right, Breaking Baddies,drop the meth.
拿回去 快拿回去吧
Pick up the meth!Pick up the meth!
这个最好是开胃前戏
This better be dinner theater!
现在 百味猪排
And now,pork chops 100 ways.
100块猪排
100 pork chops!
我不敢相信老爸竟然错过了这个
I can't believe Dad is missing this.
的确 你爸确实很有趣 不过我也很有趣
Sure, your dad's great,but I'm fun, too.
看我吃这个
Look at me eat, huh?
我在骗谁呢?
Who am I kidding?
这些东西我一点都不想吃了
I'm not enjoying this.
就连这泡沫尝起来也索然无味
Even the foam tastes like nothing.
我还是给 Homer挂个电话吧
I'm calling Homer.
啊Marge
Marge!
这根本不是什么美食餐馆
This isn't a food restaurant!
这是个冰毒工厂
It's a meth restaurant!
是个冰毒工厂
A meth-taurant! Aah!
美食家们 帮帮我
Foodies, help me!
我的丈夫有危险
My husband's in danger!
我们现在还不能离开这里
Oh, we can't leave now.
我们还没品尝在外太空的
We haven't had the root vegetables
绝对真空中烹制的炖菜呢
cooked in the perfect vacuum of outer space.
他们说除非你吃过了零重力培植的芹菜萝卜
They say you can't even understand parsnips
不然你不可能了解它真正的味道
until you had zero-g parsnips.
你怎么能就这样扬长而去!
How dare you walk out on me!
你的甜点放在这个狗食袋(餐馆给顾客把残羹剩菜带回喂狗的袋子)里了
Your dessert is in this doggie bag
这是用蓝莓喂养的蜘蛛的丝编织而成的
woven from the silk of a blueberry-fed spider.
带上它走吧
Take it and go!
我勒个去
Ah, shucks.
我们全家打扮的漂漂亮亮的来
We get the family dressed up to go
参观我们最喜欢的冰毒作坊 结果这里却被围剿了
to our favorite meth lab,and it's all raided out.
亲爱的 我还是更喜欢
Oh, honey,I always liked
你亲自给我做的那些玩意
your home-cooked better anyways.
你这是要去哪?
Uh, where do you think you're going?
作为妻子我必须向我的丈夫认错啊
A wife needs to tell her husband she was wrong.
进去吧
And in you go.
对不起
Sorry.
你在这的所作所为给我带来了不小的麻烦
Everything you've done here has created problems.
我得救救他
I've got to save him.
我的甜点
My dessert.
尝尝这解构了的苹果派吧
Eat deconstructed apple pie!
妈妈 谢谢你给我做的苹果派
Merci, Maman,pour la tarte tatin à la mode.
Marge 你害了我又救了我
Oh, Marge,you saved me from the danger you put me in.
我又高兴又生气
I am so happy and angry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我想我只是想让孩子们像崇拜你
I guess I just wanted the kids
一样崇拜我
to look at me the way they look at you.
老妈 这可真了不起
Wow, Mom!That was awesome.
我们这一天里吃了疯狂的科技大餐的
We ate mad-scientist food
同时又摧毁了这个冰毒作坊
and broke up a meth lab in the same day.
给力老妈 给力老妈
Fun Mom! Fun Mom!
给力老妈
Fun Mom!
这才是我喜欢的泡沫饮料
Now, that's my kind of foam.
这真不错
This is nice.
一个家庭游乐日
A family fun day.
这是50块钱
Here's 50 bucks.
接下来的两个小时
For the next two hours,
不要让我看到你们一眼
I don't want to know you exist.
家庭游乐日
Family fun day.
* 我们开了个美食博客 *
* We're bloggin' a food blog *
* 设置好我们的账号 *
* Settin' up accounts for our users *
* 在电脑上 *
* Usin' computers *
* 每天发推特 *
* Post tweets every day *
* 每天推特 *
* Yo, yo,tweets every day, y'all *
* 从不给四星评价 *
* Never give it four stars *
* 从没给过四星评价 *
* Ain't never give it four stars *
* 也许是二星 也许是三星 *
* Maybe two, maybe three *
* 维护访客评论 *
* Moderatin' the comments *
* 检查页面 页面 页面 *
* Checkin' the page views,page views, page views *
* 鸭子的脂肪 *
* Duck fat *
* 松露的油 *
* Truffle oil, yo, yo, yo *
* 我的美食就是艺术 我的美食就是艺术 *
* My food is art,my food is art *
* 发自我的内心 *
* It comes right from the heart. *